arthurfindlaycollege.org 2016-05-16

# AFC Privacy Policy

This privacy policy sets out how The Arthur Findlay College (The AFC) uses and protects any information that you give when you use this website.

The AFC is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

The AFC may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 1st May 2010.

**We may collect the following information**

  * name
  * country of residence
  * contact information as an email address
  * details of products and services that you are interested in

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: 

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We will periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided by subscription.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

**Security**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

**We DO NOT use cookies**

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. 

**Links to other websites**

Our website contains links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

**Controlling your personal information**

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: 

  * whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by emailing us at: [ _webmanager@arthurfindlaycollege.org_](mailto:webmanager@arthurfindlaycollege.org) or use the ' _Unsubscribe_ ' link on the website.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee will be payable. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to: The General Manager, The Arthur Findlay College, Stansted Hall, Stansted, Essex, United Kingdom, CM24 8UD.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
